ONYEBUEKE IFEANYI SAMUEL

onyebuekes93@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/onyebueke-i feanyi-1b52411b4/ www.github.com/Samuel202093 https://samuel-onyebueke.netlify.a pp +2348131880839

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer, Port-Harcourt — Fullstack Developer

January 2022 - PRESENT

I developed and maintained web applications using Html5, Css, Tailwind Css, Javascript, ReactJs, Nodejs, Express, Mongodb, Postgresql.

I designed and implemented RESTful APIs to facilitate seamless communication between the frontend and backend..

I implemented authentication and authorization mechanisms for the backend for security of user's data using JWT.

I integrated third-party APIs and services to enhance the functionality of the application.

I refactored the code base to optimize the application.

I implemented continuous integration and deployment (CI/CD) pipelines using git.

Loc Tech I.T Institute, Port-Harcourt — Web developer Intern

October 2020 - December 2021

I participated in an intensive coding bootcamp, honing my programming skills and collaborating with other students to develop innovative projects.

Community Secondary School Ojiegbe, Ebony — Teacher (NYSC PPA)

August 2019 - August 2020

I.C.T Instructor

ABOUT

Gender: Male

Marital Status: Single,

Nationality: Nigeria

State: Anambra

L.G.A: Orumba-south

Language: English

PROFILE

A highly accomplished and result driven graduate in Computer Engineering who is keen in applying academic foundation and technical experience. Accustomed to providing integral technical support. Experience in Microsoft Word, Website Design and Development and also have the ability to function independently and in fast-paced team environments.

EDUCATION

Federal Polytechnic Oko, Anambra — HND

November 2016 - November 2018

Computer Engineering

Federal Polytechnic Oko, Anambra — ND

October 2013 - August 2015

Computer Engineering

Immanuel Comprehensive High School, Port-Harcourt —

WAEC

September 2005 - August 2011

WAEC

HOBBIES

- Coding
- Reading Books
- Listening Music
- Surfing the Internet
- Playing games

REFEREES

Mr. Chuku Raymond

Software Engineer Rivers I.C.T Center(Techcreek) Port-Harcourt.

Tel: 08077373982

Mr. Duff Ini. D. Caleb

Software Instructor Rivers I.C.T Center(Techcreek) Port-Harcourt. Tel: 08068800748

CAREER OBJECTIVES

To make a positive impact and attain professional distinction of organization through application of acquired skills, providing top quality services and enhancing organizational goals and visions.

SKILLS

Proficient in Html, Css, Tailwind Css, Javascript, ReactJs, Redux, Bootstrap, NodeJs, MongoDb, Next Js and React Native in view, Postgresql, computer literacy, efficient time management, excellent communication, adept to new technologies, team-player, excellent problem-solving, creative ability and logical approach to work.